One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, 10
million dollars.  Oh,
hello, I didn't notice you here
.  Just counting
my profit from
today's
trade.  Today I
came up with a formula that I'm going to
show you guys how
you can simply
use it
to figure out
how much profit
to take as you
trade.  You can
use this
methodically to act
like a robot and
not accidentally take too much
profit off the table and
then things will go in
your favor, or you
won't take any
profit and it will
backfire on you.
And this will be the most accurate
way to be as
risk-free as possible.  Good.
So, my name is
Hunter.  This is Hunter FX and
I just finished
counting my
fake hundreds of
US dollars.  I am
Canadian.  I have
fake hundreds of
US dollars.
Anyway, this is a very
simple formula that I
just came up with
today.  Um, and we
can essentially
see where we're
going to take
profit from as the
trade progresses.  So, I
went straight to the
charts.  This will make it a little
easier to explain what
I'm talking about,
because this was the deal
I was
making today.  And I
thought about how we
can capture
profits, um, in a
mathematical
way, in a
sense.  So, that was
roughly the deal
I was making.  I
just added it.  I
think it was
about 7 hour
deals, but it's pretty
close.  And
basically I was just
entering into a
retest of this, um,
um, explosive
demand movement here.  And it was
a little higher, maybe
a little lower, but it's
not really that
important.  Now, after
it started
moving in my
favor, I started
saying, well, maybe
I want to lock in
some profit.  So,
we looked here.
We saw this wick
right here, and we
saw it
close below it.
So, we created this
sweep pattern, and I
made a video about what
this sweep pattern
could mean in the
previous video, and
I'll put a link
to it in the card there
if you want to
watch it.  This is a
strategy I
came up with.  And I saw
such a rapid
trend and I think:
well, maybe now
it can
turn around.  So
now would be a wise
time to take
profits.  What should we
do?  First, we
want to determine our
risk.  Our risk at
the moment
is...well,
let's see
how far we've
come.  First, we are
already about R2.3 into the
deal.  What I did at
this point is
obviously I
moved my stop
loss to the
breakeven point.  So,
the risk is only what
we have left to
lose on our feet.
So, our risk is the
current
stop loss placement minus R,
which we did not
execute.  So, in
this case, we have an
unrealized R of 2.34, and
our stop
loss placement is 0 R.
So, 0-2.34.  Our risk
will be 2.34.  And
our reward,
let's bring it back
here, is the remainder of the
deal.  The remainder of
the trade was
about R4 more. So
our risk/reward
here is now
2 to 4. So when we
see a possible point
where the price could
reverse, that's a very
likely place for it to
bounce and, you know,
go back to
our stop loss and
stop out here.  How are we
going to capture
the profit and how much are we
going to charge?  Well,
we just determined
that the risk is
only two, and our
reward is four.
So our reward is
twice our
risk.  So obviously
we don't want to withdraw a
large amount because we
can still win
a lot more.  So
now we can
conclude that
we actually
only want to remove 26
deals, or what is 33% of the
deal, because we are 33
% of the way to the final
deal, if you look
at it that way.
Now this changes a little bit
depending
on where
your stop is.
If your stop is still
negative, then your
risk will be higher.
So, if our stop was
still here for some reason
, our risk would
be
approximately 50%.
Since our risk
is now 3Rs,
which we can
lose, and our
reward is 4Rs.  So,
we would take even more,
or probably
about 40 or 45% of the
deal, because we have more to
lose than we have to
gain.  So let's
consider this
scenario where the price
actually went up and we
moved our stop
loss somewhere in profit.
And let's say that this take
profit point
is 2R, and our
current
unrealized price is,
let's say, 4R, just to
give us a rough
number.  And that's the point where
we think she
might change
direction when she
reaches that,
right?  For some reason, it
doesn't matter why.  Now
we go 2R minus 4R,
because that's the formula
I just
told you.  So our
risk
is now 2R on the deal
, and our reward is
whatever we have
left, maybe
three R's left on the
deal.  So our
conclusion right now is
that our
risk/reward
is about
two to three.
So, we should withdraw
even more because we don't have
much
reward left with the remaining
risk.  We have two
risks and three
rewards.  So, we
should withdraw approximately
60% from the deal.  Okay,
great.  I hope
this is
clear enough for you
guys.  And you can
use this
as a running take
profit, meaning if you
start to see
some kind of reversal, like I
just showed you, then
you can take a little bit off
at that time, depending on
how
far we've gone.  Or
you can allocate
pre-set
take profit points and then
withdraw different percentages
depending on
how far
into the trade you are.  If
you want to see
the formula, just
written down in a little
more detail, I wrote
it down on Discord in the
Risk Management section.
So join
Discord using the link
below.  And besides that,
if you like
the content, please
make sure you
hit the
subscribe button, the
like button, and
the bell, and all that stuff
.  And I'll see you
guys anytime
.  Listen.